(Penny:)Why did you tell Howard
(Penny:)I was hiding
Leonard's things?
(Bernadette:)One sec.
(Bernadette:)Why did you tell Leonard
(Bernadette:)I told you Penny was
hiding his things?!
(Howard:)It just came up
because we-we were talking
about secrets and...
(Howard:)Wait.
(Amy:)Everybody
stop it with that!
(Raj:)I'm not really a part of this,
(Raj:)so I'm just gonna dig in.
(Amy:)And I'd like to know
why you blabbed
(Amy:)about my apartment.
(Howard:)You're up, blabby.
(Bernadette:)Amy, I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have said anything.
(Amy:)I guess it's okay.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry
(Amy:)that I lied about
my apartment.
(Sheldon:)It's all right.
(Scene:)And...
(Penny:)And what?
(Penny:)Your wizard robes
are next to go.
(Raj:)Now that everything's
out on the table,
you-you think you two
will keep living together?
(Sheldon:)Despite recent events,
(Sheldon:)I do consider our experiment
(Sheldon:)in cohabitation
to have been positive.
(Amy:)Are you saying you'd like
to live with me?